Crossword Mysteries: Abracadaver is a tv movie, mystery,
crime film directed by Jonathan Wright.
During her birthday celebration, Tess and Logan find themselves swept up in a world that isn't
always what it seems when the headlining magician at the Magic Manor winds up dead.
Tess Harper, played by Lacey Chabert.
Logan O'Connor, played by Brennan Elliott.
Aunt Candace, played by Barbara Niven.
Chief Chauncey O'Connor, played by John Kapelos.
Josephine, played by Genevieve Kang.
Reed, played by Steve Belford.
Hallmark Mystery (formerly known as Hallmark Movie Channel (HMC) and Hallmark Movies & Mysteries (HMM)) is an American
digital cable and satellite television channel owned by Hallmark Media, a subsidiary of Hallmark Cards.
The channel was spun off from sister network Hallmark Channel, and airs family-oriented feature and
television films along with a limited number of murder- and mystery-themed television series.
As of February 2015, Hallmark Movies & Mysteries is available to approximately 55,827,000 pay
television households (48% of households with television) in the United States.
The tone is mind_bending.